[{"question": "https://www.zhihu.com/question/276732498", "answer": "https://www.zhihu.com/question/276732498/answer/389208151", "content": "\n\u5982\u4f55\u770b\u5f85\u300a\u5982\u4f55\u770b\u5f85 5G \u6807\u51c6\u4e0a\u8054\u60f3\u7684\u6295\u7968\uff1f\u300b\u8bdd\u9898\u7a81\u7136\u4ece\u70ed\u699c\u6d88\u5931\u7684\u73b0\u8c61\uff1f\n"}, {"question": "https://www.zhihu.com/question/26377173", "answer": "https://www.zhihu.com/question/26377173/answer/386392335", "content": "\n\u6709\u54ea\u4e9b\u5973\u6027\u5e94\u8be5\u77e5\u9053\u7684\u7537\u79d1\u5e38\u8bc6\uff1f\n"}, {"question": "https://www.zhihu.com/question/51983022", "answer": "https://www.zhihu.com/question/51983022/answer/389017060", "content": "\n\u600e\u6837\u624d\u77e5\u9053\u4e00\u4e2a\u5973\u751f\u559c\u4e0d\u559c\u6b22\u4f60\uff1f\n"}, {"question": "https://www.zhihu.com/question/35104273", "answer": "https://www.zhihu.com/question/35104273/answer/389096876", "content": "\n\u7528\u4e00\u5f20\u7eb8\u80fd\u505a\u51fa\u4ec0\u4e48 ?\n"}, {"question": "https://www.zhihu.com/question/51983022", "answer": "https://www.zhihu.com/question/51983022/answer/388978830", "content": "\n\u600e\u6837\u624d\u77e5\u9053\u4e00\u4e2a\u5973\u751f\u559c\u4e0d\u559c\u6b22\u4f60\uff1f\n"}, {"question": "https://www.zhihu.com/question/276732498", "answer": "https://www.zhihu.com/question/276732498/answer/388785998", "content": "\n\u5982\u4f55\u770b\u5f85\u300a\u5982\u4f55\u770b\u5f85 5G \u6807\u51c6\u4e0a\u8054\u60f3\u7684\u6295\u7968\uff1f\u300b\u8bdd\u9898\u7a81\u7136\u4ece\u70ed\u699c\u6d88\u5931\u7684\u73b0\u8c61\uff1f\n"}, {"question": "https://www.zhihu.com/question/276208762", "answer": "https://www.zhihu.com/question/276208762/answer/387588890", "content": "\n\u4e3a\u4ec0\u4e48\u77e5\u4e4e\u4e0a\u5f88\u591a\u4eba\u4e0d\u770b\u597d\u7279\u65af\u62c9\uff1f\n"}, {"question": "https://www.zhihu.com/question/23739325", "answer": "https://www.zhihu.com/question/23739325/answer/388815106", "content": "\n2008 \u5e74 5 \u6708 12 \u65e5\uff0c\u6c76\u5ddd\u5730\u9707\uff0c\u4f60\u4eb2\u8eab\u7ecf\u5386\u6700\u96be\u5fd8\u7684\u4e8b\u60c5\u662f\u4ec0\u4e48\uff1f\n"}, {"question": "https://www.zhihu.com/question/266222355", "answer": "https://www.zhihu.com/question/266222355/answer/387418907", "content": "\n\u5982\u679c\u5230\u4e86\u672a\u6765\uff0c\u706b\u8f66\uff0c\u5730\u94c1\u7684\u901f\u5ea6\u8fbe\u5230\u4e86 0.5 \u500d\u5149\u901f\uff0c\u90a3\u4e48\u4f1a\u53d1\u751f\u4e9b\u4ec0\u4e48\uff1f\n"}, {"question": "https://www.zhihu.com/question/50454597", "answer": "https://www.zhihu.com/question/50454597/answer/387769157", "content": "\n\u4f60\u4e3a\u4ec0\u4e48\u4f1a\u9000\u51fab\u7ad9\uff1f\n"}, {"question": "https://www.zhihu.com/question/29308650", "answer": "https://www.zhihu.com/question/29308650/answer/388160495", "content": "\n\u5f20\u6770\u88ab\u4eba\u8bf4\u571f\u662f\u56e0\u4e3a\u957f\u76f8\u5417\uff1f\n"}, {"question": "https://www.zhihu.com/question/21236058", "answer": "https://www.zhihu.com/question/21236058/answer/388036387", "content": "\n\u6b7b\u5211\u6267\u884c\u524d\u7684\u72af\u4eba\u4e00\u822c\u90fd\u662f\u4ec0\u4e48\u72b6\u6001\uff1f\n"}, {"question": "https://www.zhihu.com/question/269082692", "answer": "https://www.zhihu.com/question/269082692/answer/386764771", "content": "\n\u6709\u54ea\u4e9b\u6b4c\u66f2\u7684\u73b0\u573a\u6f14\u594f\u8ba9\u4f60\u4e45\u4e45\u4e0d\u80fd\u5fd8\u6000\uff1f\n"}, {"question": "https://www.zhihu.com/question/275460198", "answer": "https://www.zhihu.com/question/275460198/answer/383000774", "content": "\n\u4e2d\u56fd\u751f\u80b2\u7387\u4f4e\u5230\u4e86\u4ec0\u4e48\u5730\u6b65\uff1f\u4f1a\u6709\u4ec0\u4e48\u5f71\u54cd\uff1f\n"}, {"question": "https://www.zhihu.com/question/269082692", "answer": "https://www.zhihu.com/question/269082692/answer/382847300", "content": "\n\u6709\u54ea\u4e9b\u6b4c\u66f2\u7684\u73b0\u573a\u6f14\u594f\u8ba9\u4f60\u4e45\u4e45\u4e0d\u80fd\u5fd8\u6000\uff1f\n"}]